Preliminary Guide to the Lou Chibbaro Washington Blade senior reporter files (Washington Blade donation), 1980-2001 MS2245
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Long Beach, Calif extortion, undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Loose papers, undated (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Luis Alfaro, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Lutherans, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Lyle Alzada, undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
- [Lyn Stoesen file], undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
- [Lyn Stoesen file], undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Lynchburg Gay Bash, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Man says escort robbed, assualted him, 1996 January 15 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- March for Life Pro Life, undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
- March on DC conference, 1991 May (Box 13, Folder 11)
- March on Washington - Chicago meeting, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- March on Washington, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- March on Washington - LA meeting, 1992 January (Box 13, Folder 10)
- March on Washington meeting, 1991 March 09 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  This file includes reporter's notes from attending this meeting.
- March on Washington platform, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
- March on Washington platform adopted, 1992 May 10 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Marines attack Remington's patrons, 1990 June 17 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Marines shatter Remington's windows, 1990 August 26 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Marines urination incident, 1990 July 28 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Mark Barnes resigns from AIDS Action Council post, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Mark Harrington, undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Mark Hicks - Marine gay bashing, 1991 January (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Mark Iverson, undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Marsha English, 1996 June 28 - July 19 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Maryland AIDS bills, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Maryland elections, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Maryland misc, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Matlovich Cliff Anchor Congressional Cemetery Ceremony, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Mayor's AIDS announcements, 1992 May 12 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- MCC - NOVA, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
- McKinney, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Media Guide to the Lesbian and Gay Community, undated (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Medicaid, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Medicaid, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Meeting notes [1/3], undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Meeting notes [2/3], undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Meeting notes [3/3], undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Meeting notes, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Mel Wilson Dismissed as AHA Head, 1997 October 27 (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Melissa Etheridge, undated (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Methodists, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Metropolitan Community Church, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Michael Albert assualt at club bath, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Millennium March Endorsements, undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Misc. photos, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
- MMOW, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Monaghan trial - appeal and decision, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Montgomery County police chief's panel Bonnie Berger, 1991 August (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Motions, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Motions, undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
- [movie: What Makes a Family], undated (Box 60, Folder 12)
- [movie: A Girl Thing], undated (Box 60, Folder 13)
- MOW - events of week, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Mr. Bear, undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
- N.Y. Native [New York Native], undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Nadler, undated (Box 68, Folder 11)
- NAMES Project weekend, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Naples Caf, 1985 October (Box 16, Folder 14)
- NAPWA Finances, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
- National Advocacy coalition on Youth - annual conference, 1996 March 31 - April 02 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- National AIDS Organizations, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
- National AIDS Relief Foundation, undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
- National AIDS Survey, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- National Black G & L Leadership Forum, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
- National Group Survey, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- National STD Presention Conference Media Kit, undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Navy issues non-discrim. Statement Gay Fed. Workers, undated (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Navy plans to oust HIV and people, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
- New clips - Democratic Convention, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- New Hampshire passes Gay Civil Rights bill, 1997 May (Box 48, Folder 1)
- New Hill Chairs on D.C. Matters, 1997 January (Box 57, Folder 19)
- New Jersey Governor's Race, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- New York Senate crime committee dates testimony, 1982 July 26 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- New Youth Suicide Study, undated (Box 68, Folder 19)
- News Articles, undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
- News Articles, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Next Generation, undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
- NGLTF creating change conference, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
- NGLTF creating change conference, 1996 November 6 - 10 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- NGLTF head to resign? "No, not yet", 1996 March 27 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- NGLTF selects new direction, 1992 September (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Nixon tapes gay journalists?, 1996 November (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Noel Gillespie obit, 1996 June 30 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Non-discriminiation policies Gay Federal Workers Blade clippings, undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Normal, Ohio, undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Notes for stories, undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Notes, tape - Democratic convention, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- NOVA Clinic Service Awards, 1996 April 26 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- NYC Health Dept closes Stonewall bar for five days, 1996 October (Box 42, Folder 9)
- O. Henry Awards, undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Occasions, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Occasions, undated (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Officer says gays targeted by mugger at 13th and U, NW, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Old Town Holiday Inn discrimination complaint, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Olympic bath/AIDS, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
- On the air, undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Openly gay elected, appointed officials, undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Openly gay officials conference, Boston, 1990 November (Box 19, Folder 9)
- OPM Gays Gay Fed. Workers, 1993 November (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Oregon gay rights bill state Rep Chuck Carpenter, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Organizations, Gay, undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Oxandrolone, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
- P Street Beach attack - Silver Spring man arrested Doug Forsythe - witness, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
- P Street Beach ecology, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
- P Street Beach assault (police discourage pressing charges), 1995 September 09 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- P Street crime, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
- P Street gay bashing, 1995 November 27 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- P Street Police sweep, 1986 August (Box 17, Folder 9)
- P Street violence, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- P.E.N., undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Pannell - Stein Club flap, 1996 March (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Park police surveillance photos - Black Forest, 1984 October (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Pataki executive orders, 1996 April 09 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Patricia Cornwell, mystery in lesbian love affair, 1996 June 28 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Paul Cane disappears, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
- PCP, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
- People of Color and AIDS, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  This file includes issues of The Malebox DC's largest Publication for Black Gay Men August 1996, September 1996, and 3rd anniversary issue
- Performances, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Perot, Bush interviews ABC News, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
- PETA, undated (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Pflag, undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Phase I Shooting, undated (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia story - Rita Adessa and PLGTF, undated (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Phill Wilson considered for White House AIDS post, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Philly to DC AIDS Ride, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Philly-DC AIDS ride, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Pick pocket scam - fag bars, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Pills, pills, pills, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Pinkerton hit with $10 million judgement in gay bashing suit, 1996 November (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Police chief Larry Soulsby interview, 1995 November 17 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Police raid "cheers", 1987 March 14 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Police, undated (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Possible gay murder - Nassau County, NY, [Phillip Greco], 1984 December 21 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Post Democratic convention issues, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Poz Life Expo '96, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Poz Life Expo '97, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Prep - Larry Frankel, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Presidential Advisory council on AIDS, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Presidential AIDS Council Resignations?, undated (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Presidential Election info, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Presidential inscription placed on Matlovich grave, undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Pride Fest '97, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Prime boys escor arrest, 1986 April 10 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Prince William Gay and Lesbian Association, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Probate dispute/AIDS death (Library of Congress), undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Project Open Mind, undated (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Protease Inhibitor, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Protease success stories, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Psychiatric survivors demo [unintelligible word] gays, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Puerto Rico Regulation, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Quayle at party, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Queer Cartoons, undated (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Queer Comics, undated (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Rainbow Radio, undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Rand corp. report, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Rape Protection Act of 1985 - Clarke bill - (sodomy repeal), undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Real estate agents, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Records of owners of gay bars, undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Re-election, undated (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Rehoboth Death - Paige Bendini, 1997 June 08 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Rehoboth storm damage "Nor Easter", 1998 February (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Rep. Charles Taylor (R-NC) "Martin", undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Rep. Jim Kolbe (R-AZ) comes out, 1996 August 02 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Report of receipts and expenditures for candidate or political committee, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
- [reporter's notes with interviews], undated (Box 60, Folder 16)
  The folder includes subject such as ENDA and FACE.
- [reporter's notes with interviews], undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
  This folder includes subject such as ENDA and politics.
- [reporter's notebooks for various subjects], undated (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Republican Campaigns (Allen's PAC and pledge for honest change), undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Republican convention - plans for protest, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Republican Convention, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Republican Convention, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  This folder includes reporters notes of events and represents a detailed description from someone at these events.
- Republicans - Presidential Election, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Resources of Education and Counseling Faculty, 1996 June (Box 52, Folder 18)
  Project for the Integration of Gay and Lesbian Youth Issues in School Personnel Certification Programs. Prepared by Arthur Lipkin, Ed.D, Project Director, Massachusetts Governor's Commission on Gay and Lesbian Youth, Project Advisors
- Retrovir (zidovudine), undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Rev. Burris/St. Clair, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Rhode Island propose gay rights bill, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Ric Grenell Post feature (Rep. Mark Sanford-R-S.C., undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Richard Burns, undated (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Richard Socarides profile, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Richards v. Mileski, et al, (1950's investigation of Gays in State Dept.), undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Right-wing hate groups (white supremacists - neo-Nazi), undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
- RNC Chair Jim Nicholson, 1997 February (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Roanoke Murder, undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Robert Merritt - young Dillenger, undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Robert Wood Johnson Foundation Grant, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Rodney Wood - theft prosecution, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Roger Guy - missing person, 1996 April (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Roy Mason murder, 1996 June 07 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Roy Richard's "Theory" about U.S. Gay Chinese Group, undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Rudy Galindo, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Rush Limbaugh, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Ryan White CARE Act, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Ryan White, undated (Box 59, Folder 6)
- San Vito, Italy - US Air Force purge, 1990 October (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Saudi con man, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Sawyer/Bauman, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Schindler update, 1993 March 05 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Science Magazine article - AIDS prevelance/risky behavior on straights, 1992 November (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Scott to Leave as White House Gay Liaison?, undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Seaman Amy Barnes case - Navy witch hunt, 1996 March (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Security Clearance Commission discusses Gays; Gay Fed Workers, 1994 February (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Select few raid-related story, 1979-1982 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Senate - Hate Crimes Amendment, 1996 September 10 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Senate Judiciary hearing on Hate Crimes Act, 1996 March 19 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Senate passes indecency amendment to publi broadcasting bill, 1992 June 03 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Serkan Altan update "summoned to Turkish Embassy", 1995 April (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Serodiscordant couples, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
- "Sex scandal" Blade clips, undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Shearn Moody Houston "scam", 1986 December - 1987 December (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Shenandoah hikers merdered - press coverage, 1996 June (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Showtime movie Execution of Justice, undated (Box 64, Folder 7)
- SMYAL cuts budget, reduces services, 1995 October (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Socarides appointed Gay liaison at White House with highest rank, 1997 February 24 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Sodomy arrests, 1992 February 25 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Sodomy at Clinic House, 1992 July 29 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Sodomy repeal hearing DC Council, 1993 January 29 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Sons of police official arrested at P Street Beach, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Sojourner Loses State Committee Election, 1997 August 20 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Special D.C. Council Election, Dixon, Catania, et. al, 1997 December 02 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Speeches - Democratic Convention, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Stadtlanders, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Stars magazine raid, undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
- State committee slate Vorndram -Bustamente flap, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
- State Dept. issues non-discrim. Policies (Warren Christopher) Gay Fed. Workers, 1994 April 22 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- State of local movement, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
- State survey of gay bills, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Stein club endorses council candidate, 1996 July 15 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Stein Club news analysis, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Mayor endorses Rolark Stein club presidential endorsement, 1992 April (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Stein Club info, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Stein club, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Stein meeting, 1992 August 10 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  This reporter attended the Gertrude Stein Democratic Club meeting and noted what took place.
- Steno book - Erie Monaghan trial, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Steno book - Erie Monaghan trial, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Steno book - Les Powell arrest, GAA Meeting, Gay community forum, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Steve Michael campaign, undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Strangulation attempt "pick-up" case Stacy Bridges, 1997 July 07 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Study on homosexuality and older brothers, 1996 January (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Summit meeting, 1993 January (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Sundance film festival press packet, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Swim for Life, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
- TB,[Tuberculosis], undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Tear Sheets, undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Teen Suicide Issue Update, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Television, undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Television and movies, 2000-2001 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  File identified as reporter Bill Roundy's file. This file includes a 3.5 floppy disc with an obiturary for Donna Davis.
- Television show press release, 1999-2000 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Terrence Johnson, undated (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Texas GOP platform keeps anti-gay, 1992 June (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Thesaurus of Gay and Lesbian Index Terms, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Thesaurus for indexing, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Thomas Glave, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Three Anne Arundel youths charged with murder, sexual assualt of 16-year old male, 1995 August 13 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Thurmond named head of White House AIDS Office, undated (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Tim McFeely - HRCF, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Tinky Winky, undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
- To Be Edited in Comp. Files, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Toby Reece suicide, 1997 January 25 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Tom Duane complains about "no" Clinton appointees, 1997 May 13 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Tom Swann U.S. Navy, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
- "Tops" Escort Agency Raided, 1997 August 08 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Toxo, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Tracks gang crime, 1995 June (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Tracks kidnapping sexual assault, 1987 May 14 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Transcripts, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Transcripts [1/3], undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Transcripts [2/3], undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Transcripts [3/3], undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Transgenders challenge Lorton "ban", 1997 August (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Transportation, Agriculture issue "Gay Policies" Gay Federal Workers, undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Treatment Action Group, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Trinity College, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Troy Watson shooting [4th street NW], 1996 March 30 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Trumpets mace incident, 1995 November 09 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- TV Out, undated (Box 68, Folder 5)
- TV Reference, undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Two gay men sue housing group for discrimination, 1995 September (Box 7, Folder 4)
- U.S. Dept. of Education "Guidelines" on Harassment, "Anti-Gay", 1997 March 13 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- U.S. Prosecutor says Justice Dept. Policy of Gays Doesn't Reach Field Offices, undated (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Uncle Ed scandal in Philadelphia, 1992 April (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Unibomber criticizes gays, 1995 August (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Union Station flap Gays-security office, 1996 May 08 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Unitarian Church forum - gays in the military, 1993 April 18 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Upcoming out of town, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Update Food and Friends, undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Urine HIV test, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
- US District Court judge overturns indecency law, 1992 June 23 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- US Hate Crimes statitstics act expires, 1995 December 31 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- V.J., undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
- VA 1995 State Elections - Candidates, undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
- VA '96 Election, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- VA AIDS, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
- VA AG rules against gays in domestic violence court, 1995 July (Box 8, Folder 9)
- VA background stories, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
- VA Baptists, undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
- VA Budgets Ax AIDS - Fairfax rescued, 1996 April 11 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- VA Candidates Ratings - Nov. '95 Election, 1995 November (Box 53, Folder 13)
- VA Candidates, undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
- VA Election, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- VA Elections, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- VA '96 Election, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- VA Elections, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
- VA Gays Wary of GOP takeover/ratings, 1995 October 27 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- VA GOP Senate Primary, undated (Box 53, Folder 11)
- VA Human Rights Council, undated (Box 63, Folder 7)
- VA Phone Lists, undated (Box 53, Folder 19)
- VA Races, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- VA Sodomy Law, undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
- VA Special Elections, undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
- VA University benefits, undated (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Va. State Police "anti-Gay harrassment" (near Dulles Airport), 1997 March 11 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Vacation records, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Van spray paint incident, 1995 November (Box 8, Folder 5)
- VA's Secret, undated (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Venus nomenclature, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Vermont Backlash, undated (Box 65, Folder 13)
- VHDA - First Vote to Kill Loans, 1995 December 22 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- VHDA restricts loans (public hearing and final vote), 1995 January 26 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Viatical flap - DOD, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Viaticals - Bill of Rights, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Viaticals - downturn, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Viaticals and the SEC, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Viaticals, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Viral load, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Virginia Bills, undated (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Virginia gays run in Democratic caucuses, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Virginia HOPWA loss of funds, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Virginia Partisans - gay democratic group, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Virginia Partisans Endorse 63 Gays in Dem. Caucuses, 1996 April 12 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Virginia Partisans, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Virginia, undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Virginians for Justice, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Virginians for Justice, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Visitation Rights and AIDS, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Vistide (cidofovir), undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Voter AIDS funding survey, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Voter Info '96, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- VT auditor comes out, Ed Flanagan, 1995 August 05 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- W. Post nixes domestic partner plan, 1996 November (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Walt Whitman Community School, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Wan Lee Ing case, undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Ward 6 Special Election, undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Warren / Escort, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Wasting, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Water filters, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Water safety, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Wet bar/gender discrimination complaint, 1995 November 27 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Wet-Edge bankruptcy update - back taxes for cover charges, undated (Box 48, Folder 20)
- John Vitullo court documents white envelope, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- [White House], 1990-1997 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- White House Debate over Colo. Amicus Brief, 1995 May 31 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- White House gloves, undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
- White House Hate Crimes Conference, 1997 November 10 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- White House health care meeting, 1993 April 16 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- White House meeting - Gay elected officials, 1995 June 13 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- White House meeting - Gays in military, 1993 March 26 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- White House Press Secretary Mike McCurry, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
- White House Response to Gay Marriage Issue, undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Whitman - Walker board meetings, 1992 September 14 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Whitman-Walker Clinic case workers flap, 1997 June (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Whitman-Walker Clinic Blade classified seeking person who took HIV test, 1995 April 12 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- WHO/UN, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Will and Grace, undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
- William Burroughs, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Winchell Murder - KY, undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Women & HIV, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Workplace Fairness Act ("ENDA Alternative"), undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Workplace training, (Federal), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
- World AIDS Day, undated (Box 64, Folder 9)
- World AIDS Day, undated (Box 65, Folder 14)
- World II, undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
- World III, undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
- World Nov. '95, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- WORLD/week, undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Would be assassin, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
- WWC/Nova, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Wyatt Wood, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Youth Pride day, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Youth Pride, undated (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Youth summit, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)